<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Secure on Foundries.io</title><link>https://foundries.io/tags/secure/</link><description>Recent content in Secure on Foundries.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundries.io/tags/secure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Case Study: Aeler C3 shipping containers assured with complete chain of trust with FoundriesFactory</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2020/06/22/20200622-aeler-c3-containers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2020/06/22/20200622-aeler-c3-containers/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Aeler is a Swiss AI-driven company designing hardware and software to meet fundamental logistics requirements by revamping the standard shipping container. Aeler envisions a world where logistics operations are efficient, clean and intelligent. To that end, they believe that building the next-gen intermodal container, one of global trade’s core components, will enable a new era of both economical and environmental efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Case Study: Robotic vacuum cleaners made secure for life</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2020/05/18/20200518-robotic-vacuum-cleaners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2020/05/18/20200518-robotic-vacuum-cleaners/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Maidbot provides safe and cost efficient automated systems, delivering unprecedented
value to hotel operators, room attendants and hotel guests. Their flagship product,
Rosie, is the world&amp;rsquo;s first housekeeping robot, cleaning the floors of small and
large spaces in hotels, airports, shopping malls and universities. She also
functions as an indoor mobile data platform, collecting and analyzing invaluable
and actionable business data including temperature, air quality and foot traffic.
Using LiDAR technology to navigate, Rosie has omnidirectional wheels for ease of movement.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>