<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Raspberry Pi on Foundries.io</title><link>https://foundries.io/tags/raspberry-pi/</link><description>Recent content in Raspberry Pi on Foundries.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundries.io/tags/raspberry-pi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The OTA updatable OS for your next IoT or Edge Product</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/07/05/20190705-ota-updatable-os/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/07/05/20190705-ota-updatable-os/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Why is there no Android or Red Hat Enterprise Linux for IoT and Edge devices? The &amp;ldquo;one size fits all&amp;rdquo; approach of a modern Linux distro does not meet the requirements of the IoT and Edge markets because of the diversity of hardware and use cases - from cellular-connected sensors, to industrial IoT infrastructure, to gateways and even autonomous vehicle computing. More complex use-cases and more powerful processors almost universally use some variant of Linux. Simpler devices such as sensors typically use an RTOS. In this article we focus on Linux - a future article will explore the many RTOS options.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Google Assistant on the LmP</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2018/05/09/google-assistant-on-the-lmp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2018/05/09/google-assistant-on-the-lmp/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;In this blog, I describe how to run the Google Assistant SDK on a Raspberry Pi with an external speaker and microphone. After you get things configured and gather key pieces of information you&amp;rsquo;ll have a simple, portable and easy to reproduce Google Assistant appliance.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Linux microPlatform, now with OTA updates (beta)</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2018/04/11/20180411-over-the-air/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2018/04/11/20180411-over-the-air/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting with Linux microPlatform update 0.13, we are including support for over-the-air (OTA) updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>180 days</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2018/03/30/20180330_goodfriday_180days/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2018/03/30/20180330_goodfriday_180days/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s March 30, 2018, Good Friday, and it has been 180 days since we started Foundries.io. In this time, we established our initial infrastructure, created the first microPlatform products and, on March 27, we produced our 12th update to the microPlatforms, roughly 1 update every 2 weeks. When we started the microPlatforms, we wanted to get our systems and processes running smooth enough to provide meaningful software updates that could be integrated into products by our subscribers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may think that consuming software updates every 2 weeks is daunting, however, the upstream projects are ever-evolving and in this same period, Zephyr has seen 3,385 commits and the Linux Kernel has seen 28,876 commits and we aren’t even listing the changes of the other software projects. Long story short, with all this activity, there are new features and fixes that affect all aspects of computing that your products may have missed out on. With the microPlatforms we have created a product that not only keeps you close to the latest software, but standards-based and fully tested end-to-end for use within connected IoT products.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>