<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lmp on Foundries.io</title><link>https://foundries.io/tags/lmp/</link><description>Recent content in Lmp on Foundries.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundries.io/tags/lmp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Keeping Edge devices secure from IoT hackers</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/07/15/20190715-secure-edge-devices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/07/15/20190715-secure-edge-devices/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Edge devices are now at the frontline of security attacks on manufacturing and enterprise organisations. Hackers are extorting more money out of a wider range of companies and corporations, with the latest estimates being that attacks have increased by 500% in the last year.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The OTA updatable OS for your next IoT or Edge Product</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/07/05/20190705-ota-updatable-os/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/07/05/20190705-ota-updatable-os/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Why is there no Android or Red Hat Enterprise Linux for IoT and Edge devices? The &amp;ldquo;one size fits all&amp;rdquo; approach of a modern Linux distro does not meet the requirements of the IoT and Edge markets because of the diversity of hardware and use cases - from cellular-connected sensors, to industrial IoT infrastructure, to gateways and even autonomous vehicle computing. More complex use-cases and more powerful processors almost universally use some variant of Linux. Simpler devices such as sensors typically use an RTOS. In this article we focus on Linux - a future article will explore the many RTOS options.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Foundries.io makes IoT deployable using Linux and Zephyr microPlatforms™</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/06/05/20190605-deployable-iot-zmp-lmp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/06/05/20190605-deployable-iot-zmp-lmp/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;brings-secure-supportable-longevity-to-iot-installed-devices&#34;&gt;Brings secure, supportable longevity to IoT installed devices&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LONDON, UK; 5 June 2019: Foundries.io, innovator in the deployment of Linux and Zephyr for Edge and IoT solutions, announces key customers showcasing its ability to provide secure, supportable platforms, realising the full value of IoT.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>