<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Foundriesfactory on Foundries.io</title><link>https://foundries.io/tags/foundriesfactory/</link><description>Recent content in Foundriesfactory on Foundries.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundries.io/tags/foundriesfactory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Case Study: Robotic vacuum cleaners made secure for life</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2020/05/18/20200518-robotic-vacuum-cleaners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2020/05/18/20200518-robotic-vacuum-cleaners/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Maidbot provides safe and cost efficient automated systems, delivering unprecedented
value to hotel operators, room attendants and hotel guests. Their flagship product,
Rosie, is the world&amp;rsquo;s first housekeeping robot, cleaning the floors of small and
large spaces in hotels, airports, shopping malls and universities. She also
functions as an indoor mobile data platform, collecting and analyzing invaluable
and actionable business data including temperature, air quality and foot traffic.
Using LiDAR technology to navigate, Rosie has omnidirectional wheels for ease of movement.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Secure IoT Linux Platform FoundriesFactory Sees Adoption from Startups to Enterprise</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2020/02/24/20200224-lmp-adoption/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2020/02/24/20200224-lmp-adoption/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Aeler, Maidbot and Spriteguard select scalable embedded Linux platform for rapid development, deployment and management of connected Edge devices&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Foundries.io Investment and the FoundriesFactory</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/10/24/20191024-investment-and-factory/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/10/24/20191024-investment-and-factory/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;After more than two years in development we have accomplished two major milestones in the last month. We have announced our first equity round of $3.5M, and we have introduced FoundriesFactory - a cloud service to help companies development secure, deploy and continually maintain products through their complete lifecycle - for IoT and Edge applications, accelerating time to market and reducing costs.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Foundries.io raises $3.5 million to fix security and device management for IoT and Edge</title><link>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/10/22/20191022-foundriesio-funding-fix-iot-security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/insights/2019/10/22/20191022-foundriesio-funding-fix-iot-security/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Cambridge, UK, 22nd October 2019: Foundries.io, a leading open IoT platform company, today announces a $3.5M funding round to advance its secure operating system platform. The round is led by Crane Venture Partners, with participation from Backed VC.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>