<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Partners on Foundries.io</title><link>https://foundries.io/partners/</link><description>Recent content in Partners on Foundries.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://foundries.io/partners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://foundries.io/partners/all/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/partners/all/</guid><description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;navbar.html&#34; . }} OUR PARTNERS
Partners and building a collaborative ecosystem is key to Foundries.io. Partnership with Foundries.io can provide you with easy-to-use, secure, OTA updatable scalable software platforms. The microPlatforms from Foundries.io can accelerate your time to market whilst enabling you to focus on your product differentiators. Below are some of the initial partners already gaining benefits from working with Foundries.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://foundries.io/partners/linaro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/partners/linaro/</guid><description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;navbar.html&#34; . }} OUR PARTNERS
Linaro Contact partner Overview Linaro&amp;#39;s mission is to lead collaboration in the Arm&amp;#174; ecosystem by bringing together industry and the open source community to work on key projects, deliver great tools, reduce industry wide fragmentation and redundant effort, and provide common software foundations for all.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://foundries.io/partners/toradex/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/partners/toradex/</guid><description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;navbar.html&#34; . }} OUR PARTNERS
Toradex Contact partner Overview Toradex is based in Switzerland with offices around the world, offering Arm&amp;#174;-based System on Modules (SoMs) and customized SBCs. Powered by NXP&amp;#174; i.MX 6, i.MX 7, i.MX 8 and Vybrid; and NVIDIA&amp;#174; Tegra 2, 3 and TK1 SoCs, these pin-compatible SoMs offer scalability in terms of price, performance, power consumption and I/Os.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://foundries.io/partners/zephyr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/partners/zephyr/</guid><description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;navbar.html&#34; . }} OUR PARTNERS
Zephyr Contact partner Overview The Zephyr&amp;#8482; Project is a scalable real-time operating system (RTOS) supporting multiple hardware architectures, optimised for resource constrained devices, and built with safety and security in mind. The project is hosted by the Linux Foundation uniting leaders from across the industry to build a best-in-breed small scalable RTOS.</description></item></channel></rss>