<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Openings on Foundries.io</title><link>https://foundries.io/openings/</link><description>Recent content in Openings on Foundries.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundries.io/openings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Foundries.io Embedded Software Engineer, Platform Security (Remote)</title><link>https://foundries.io/openings/20200918-platform-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/openings/20200918-platform-security/</guid><description>Description At Foundries.io we have created an open source software platform using the latest industry practices and standards throughout, so product developers can build on a common software base. Our aim is for cross-industry adoption, with no lock-in. To accomplish this we use industry standards and a new business model to disrupt the status quo of the fragmented IoT device market.
We’re looking for an embedded engineer to lead our platform security development.</description></item><item><title>Foundries.io Technical Writer (Remote)</title><link>https://foundries.io/openings/20200527-techwriter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundries.io/openings/20200527-techwriter/</guid><description>Description At Foundries.io, our vision is to deliver an open, customizable, secure OS and firmware platform for an IoT/Edge product’s lifetime. We aim for cross-industry adoption, with no lock-in. We use industry standards and a new business model to disrupt the status quo of the fragmented IoT device market.
The driving force behind this success is our unwavering belief in clear and effective communication. We’re searching for an experienced technical writer to join our team and help take our customer-focused software as a service to new heights.</description></item></channel></rss>